bulkprchecker.net 2015-02-11

# Privacy Policy - Google Pagerank Checker - BulkPRChecker.net

**BulkPRChecker.net** , with this privacy policy, would like to demonstrate our commitment to the privacy of the users and consumers of our website. Please read the following to understand how we treat any personally identifiable information collected from our visitors and users. 

## Collection and use of Personal Information

You are free to use the content of BulkPRChecker.net without having to provide any personal information whatsoever. For normal web usage, we do not collect any personal information from our visitors nor do we track the visitor information such as IP address. However, the hosting provider may log low level technical information (such as visitor IP address, duration of visit, visited pages etc) about each visitor and we normally do not use nor publish this information. Any information that is collected while you contact us via the contact form will not be shared with third-parties nor do we store such information on any permanent storage. We hate spam as much as you do. 

We do not store the URLs submitted or their page rank information on our systems. 

Any browser cookies that may be set by the website builder, content management system, Google analytics or supporting software etc, can be turned off at anytime by modifying your Internet browser’s settings. 

We are not responsible for the republishing of the content found on this website on other web sites or media without our permission. 

## DoubleClick DART Cookie

Whenever we enable Google ads on this site, Google as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on the site. 

Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to the website and other sites on the Internet. 

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>. 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include – Google Adsense and Clickbank and various individual affiliate products. 

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on the send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

The website has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. This website’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

This privacy policy is subject to change without notice. 

If you have any further question, please feel free contact us. 

This page was last updated on 6 June 2012
